<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Chapter 6 on College Algebra</title>
    <link>https://duragauge.github.io/chapter-6/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Chapter 6 on College Algebra</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    
	<atom:link href="https://duragauge.github.io/chapter-6/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>6.1 Systems of Equations</title>
      <link>https://duragauge.github.io/chapter-6/6.1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://duragauge.github.io/chapter-6/6.1/</guid>
      <description>Image by Tayeb MEZAHDIA from Pixabay Introduction Many of the images we see in movies, videos, games and in print are created and edited by computer graphics software. Artists, designers, architects and engineers use computer generated images to make simulations, prototypes, animations, life-like models and stunningly realistic visual effects.
The shapes and surfaces that comprise computer generated images are created by mathematical equations.
In order for these shapes and surfaces to fit together seamlessly and move smoothly their equations often need to satisfy several parameters simultaneously.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>6.2 Sequences</title>
      <link>https://duragauge.github.io/chapter-6/6.2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://duragauge.github.io/chapter-6/6.2/</guid>
      <description>Image by RitaE from PixabayIntroduction When shopping at a grocery store it makes no difference if you grab eggs or flour first. As long as you get everything on your list you&#39;ll be fine.
But a recipe is much different than a shopping list. A recipe is an ordered list of instructions. If you want the dish to turn out right, you have to do each step in the proper order.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>6.3 Series</title>
      <link>https://duragauge.github.io/chapter-6/6.3/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://duragauge.github.io/chapter-6/6.3/</guid>
      <description>Image by Julia Schwab from PixabayIntroduction When Carl Friedrich Gauss  This is the same Gauss that gave us Gauss-Jordan Elimination and the Fundamental Theorem of Algebra  was a young boy in Germany it was common for students to do their work on small slate chalkboards.
The story is told that one day in 1786, when Gauss was just 9 years old, his teacher gave the class a challenging problem.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>