<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Chapter 6 on Precalculus 1 - Functions</title>
    <link>https://duragauge.github.io/chapter-6/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Chapter 6 on Precalculus 1 - Functions</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://duragauge.github.io/chapter-6/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>6.1 Algebraic Methods</title>
      <link>https://duragauge.github.io/chapter-6/6.1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://duragauge.github.io/chapter-6/6.1/</guid>
      <description>Image by Design n Print from PixabayUNDER REVISION
Objectives:
 Recognize linear, exponential, and proportional relationships from verbal descriptions. Interpret the meaning of coefficients and constants in the context of the modeled situations. Apply algebraic techniques to create equations of linear, power, and exponential functions that model real-life scenarios.  Introduction Many people are concerned about the amount of mercury they ingest by eating fish such as shark, swordfish, and tuna.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>6.2 Aligning Graphs to Data</title>
      <link>https://duragauge.github.io/chapter-6/6.2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://duragauge.github.io/chapter-6/6.2/</guid>
      <description>Tornado photo by Nikolas Noonan on UnsplashUNDER REVISION
Objectives:
 Understand and apply transformations, including shifts and stretches, to align graphs with data points. Use point-slope form and vertex form to derive equations of lines and parabolas that best fit data. Create piecewise functions by incorporating transformations. Analyze the effects of transformations in the context of the modeled situations..  Introduction Every spring, hundreds of people come to the Great Plains region of the United States in an attempt to get as close as possible to one of nature&#39;s most violent events: a tornado.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>6.3 Modeling Data</title>
      <link>https://duragauge.github.io/chapter-6/6.3/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://duragauge.github.io/chapter-6/6.3/</guid>
      <description>Image by NASAUNDER REVISION
Objectives:
 Utilize regression analysis technology, such as a graphing calculator or software, to find best-fit functions. Compare and evaluate different regression models to choose the most appropriate one for a specific data set. Use interpolation and extrapolation and address their limitations and potential errors.  Introduction When Johannes Kepler came up with his theory for the orbit of planets in 1618, he was only aware of six planets: Mercury, Venus, Earth, Mars, Jupiter and Saturn.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
